宝贝，你在外面吗？
Babe, are you out here?
是啊.
Yeah.
以为你可能是
Thought you might be.
我得走了.
I have to go soon.
好吧 好吧，我来了
Okay. Okay, I'm comin'.
来跟我说再见吧.
Come say goodbye to me.
咖啡？-打得好.
- Coffee? - Good call.
-你能在我收拾完的时候做一个吗？-当然.
- Would you make one while I finish packing? - Of course.
车马上就到.
Car should be here in a minute.
谢谢
Thank you.
哦，我的天.
Oh, my God.
西行正在经历繁忙的交通...
West bound is experiencing heavy traffic...
从610的阁楼路出口开始，一直延伸...
starting from the 610 Garret road exit and stretching...
五天没有你的咖啡我该怎么办？
What am I gonna do without your coffee for five days?
-伦敦有咖啡.是吗？
- They have coffee in London. - Do they?
对于一个从未去过的人来说，你听起来真的很确定
You sound really sure for somebody who's never been.
五天？我以为你说四个
Five days? I thought you said four.
是的 在那里呆了四天，然后我又回来过夜了
Yeah. Four days there, and then I'm back on the overnight.
没错.
Right.
你仍然可以来，你知道的
You can still come, you know.
我不能.
I can't.
我是说，有些事我想在工作中解开
I mean, there's somethin' I'm tryin' to untangle at work.
来吧.
Come on.
就这一次.冒险
Just this once. Take a risk.
下次吧.我保证.
Next time. I promise.
这是需要浇灌的东西的清单
This is a list of things that need to be watered.
周四早上，别忘了留下你的钥匙
Thursday morning, don't forget to leave your key
-麦克和他儿子的锅炉.-对.
- for Mike and his son for the boiler. - Right.
这些应该持续到我回家
Those should last until I get home.
让你想起我.
Remind you of me.
不需要提醒
Don't need reminding.
没有？
No?
你确定你会没事吗？
Are you sure you're gonna be okay?
我会没事的.
I'll be fine.
来吧.
Come on.
爱你.
Love you.
-再见.-再见.
- Bye. - Bye.
再见.
Bye.
再见!
Bye!
很高兴见到你，兄弟 是啊.是啊.
Good to see you, brother. Yeah. Yeah.
-怎么了Chuck？-嘿.
- What's going on, Chuck? - Hey.
嘿，你刚从什么地方回来？
Hey, you just back from somewhere?
穿过池塘，伙计 到处都没有
Across the pond, man. Everywhere and nowhere.
-你知道是怎么回事.-是的.
- You know how it is. - Yeah.
你只是嗡嗡地进来又出去？
You just buzzin' in and buzzin' out?
是的 我有一天的安全汇报...
Yeah. I got a day of security debrief...
然后，这是大本营，伙计
and then, it's the home base, man.
去亲吻我的小女孩
Go kiss my little girl.
这很重要.
That's important.
是的 我刚和我妻子说再见
Yeah. I just said goodbye to my wife.
嘿，伙计，你今天午饭打算吃什么？
Hey, man, what are you doing for lunch today?
-没什么？不，没有计划 是吗？
- Nothin'. No, no plans. - Yeah?
-是的.是的，我完全自由了，伙计 太棒了.
- Yeah. Yeah, I'm completely free, man. - That's great.
你知道，我有这个电脑屎
You know, I got this computer shit.
只有几个比特和字节
Just a few, like, bits and bytes
我很想让你的大脑破译
I would love to get that big brain of yours to decipher.
我发誓，上次，兄弟，你救了我的命
I swear, last time, bro, you saved my life.
-是的.是吗？
- Yeah. - Yeah?
-是的，当然.太棒了.好吧.
- Yeah, of course. - That's great. All right.
所以，你先吃午饭，
So, you go ahead and you eat your lunch,
那我来呀？
then I'll come get ya?
-是的.-我的男人.
- Yeah. - My man.
滴答，滴答，兄弟
Tick tock, tick boom, bro.
地板减二 操作
Floor Minus Two. Operations.
楼层减五 解密和分析
Floor Minus Five. Decryption and Analysis.
你好 你在吗，查理？
Hello. Are you there, Charlie?
你今天有什么要给我的，Inquiline先生？
What do you have for me today, Señor Inquiline?
2.1兆兆字节部分
2.1 terabyte tranche.
喀布尔站
Kabul Station.
2014 2022年
2014 to 2022.
独自打开这个
Open this alone.
这次不收费
No charge this time.
伊斯坦布尔的天气怎么样？
How's the weather in Istanbul?
不错的尝试
Nice try.
只是时间问题.
It's just a matter of time.
你觉得呢？
You think?
已经五年了，查理，你还在猜测
It's been five years, Charlie, and you're still guessing.
我会去的.
I'll get there.
我喜欢拼图
I like puzzles.
不像我喜欢匿名
Not as much as I like anonymity.
如果我不得不猜测，你是一个住在伊斯坦布尔的50岁俄罗斯人...
If I had to guess, you're a 50-year-old Russian man living in Istanbul...
与Reddit董事会和土耳其咖啡的亲和力
with an affinity for Reddit boards and Turkish coffee.
也许，也许不是
Perhaps, perhaps not.
我是认真的.小心这些数据
I'm serious. Be careful with this data.
这对你的机构来说是非常妥协的
It's highly compromising for your agency.
嘿.
Hey.
嗨，团队
Hi, Team.
再说一遍.你说板条箱有多大？
Tell me again. How big did you say the crate was?
20米乘10米
Twenty meters by 10.
斯莱特的另一个假设
Another one of Slater's hypotheticals.
半卡车后面的板条箱的卫星图像...
Satellite images of a crate on the back of a semi-truck...
矩形，20乘10米
rectangular in shape, 20 by 10 meters.
目的地？
Destination?
一个主要的大都市地区
A major metropolitan area.
-洛杉矶.-错误的海岸.
- LA. - Wrong coast.
卡车是从宾夕法尼亚来的吗？
Is the truck from Pennsylvania?
去DC？
Headed to DC?
到目前为止，很好
So far, so good.
-旗杆.-不，是导弹.
- A flagpole. - No, a missile.
圣诞树
Christmas tree.
白宫树总是来自宾夕法尼亚州莱顿的一个农场
The White House tree always comes from a farm in Lehighton, Pennsylvania.
卡车的尺寸告诉其余部分
And dimensions of the truck tell the rest.
-他有时候真的很烦人.-哇.
- He can be really annoying sometimes. - Wow.
那是谁？
Who's that?
大楼里最危险的人
The most dangerous man in the building.
秘密特工.砰，砰
Secret agent. Bang, bang.
他和海勒是闺蜜.
He and Heller are besties.
我是他的闺蜜.
I'm his bestie.
我们只是熟人
We're just acquaintances.
你怎么认识他的？
How do you know him?
救了他的命.
Saved his life.
海勒.
Heller.
你穿的是什么？
What are you wearing?
莎拉？
Sarah?
不是萨达姆·侯赛因.
No. Saddam Hussein.
他死了.
He's dead.
幽默，海勒
Humor, Heller.
对，对.
Right, right.
我打电话只是想让你知道我在这里
I'm just calling to let you know I'm here.
没错 我知道 我知道.我跟踪了你.
Right. I know. I know. I tracked you.
如果你不这么做，我会受伤的
I'd be hurt if you didn't.
我只是在喝咖啡
I'm just grabbing a coffee.
在等待团队其他成员的同时，试图让我保持清醒的时间
Trying to keep me awake a little bit longer while I wait for the rest of the team.
好吧.散散步.去呼吸点新鲜空气，亲爱的
All right. Take a walk. Go get some fresh air, honey.
但是我想躺下
But I want to lie down.
不 如果你躺下，你就永远站不起来
No. If you lie down, you'll never get up.
这是来自世界旅行者的圣人建议吗？
Is that sage advice from the world traveler?
苛刻
Harsh.
嘿，听着.我在这里有所发现
Hey, listen. I'm on to something here.
我可以晚点打给你吗？
Can I call you later?
是的 我爱你
Yeah. I love you.
我爱你，宝贝 再见.再见.
I love you, babe. Bye. Bye.
-再见.再见.-再见.
- Bye. Bye. - Bye.
-再见.-再见.
- Bye. - Bye-bye.
搞什么鬼？
What the hell?
有无人机袭击的目击者报告...
There are witness reports of a drone strike...
但是美国消息人士证实这是一名自杀炸弹手
but U.S. sources have confirmed that it was a suicide bomber.
-袭击的规模被摧毁了...-有150人被杀...
- The scale of the attacks devastated... - Some 150 people killed...
包括法国特种部队
including French special forces.
七名丹麦海军陆战队员在爆炸中丧生...
Seven Danish marines were killed in the explosion...
最初被报道为误导性空袭
which was initially reported as a misdirected air strike.
国防部发言人...
A Department of Defense spokesman...
否认美国空军在该地区行动的报道...
denied reports of U.S. Air Force operations in the area...
将袭击归咎于当地叛乱分子
blaming the attack on local insurgents.
Moore警长.
Chief Moore.
嘿，伙计.
Hey, buddy.
卡洛斯.
Carlos.
你没事吧？你看起来像个该死的鬼
You okay? You look like a damn ghost.
我只是在纠正一些...
I was just rectifying some...
查理？
Charlie?
一些文件
Some files.
好的.
Okay.
我可能找了一个不该找的地方
I may have looked somewhere I shouldn't have.
在我们部门？
Within our department?
灰色区域
Gray area.
我们不做灰色地带，查理
We don't do gray areas, Charlie.
我们的工作绝对是二进制的
Our work is decidedly binary.
那就不行.
Then, no.
在这种情况下，你要做的就是保持安静
In that case, what you do is you keep quiet.
是啊.
Yeah.
嘿，我要么很忙，要么把手机掉在包底了
Hey, I'm either busy or dropped my cell at the bottom of my bag.
告诉我你是谁，我会给你回电话
Tell me who you are and I'll call you back.
嘿，是我.
Hey, it's me.
想念你.
Miss you.
我先浇花
I will water the flowers first thing.
打电话给我.
Call me.
-Moore警长.-查理.
- Chief Moore. - Charlie.
对不起，我不经常在这里看到你，先生
I'm sorry, I don't see you down here very often, sir.
你为什么要这么做？
Why would you?
你的办公室不错
Nice office you have.
是的 是的，如果你不喜欢阳光或新鲜空气
Yeah. Yeah, if you don't like sunlight or fresh air.
对于苔藓或地衣或蘑菇...
For a moss or a lichen or mushrooms...
查理，你一直在追踪新闻吗？
Charlie, have you been tracking the news?
嗯，我还在努力找到一个我可以信任的出路
Well, I'm still tryin' to find an outlet I can trust.
当我们今天早上听说你在这里时，我们就是这么想的
That's what we thought when we heard you were here this morning.
我们？
We?
我需要你和我一起去主任办公室
I need you to come with me to the Director's office.
求你了.
Please.
七楼 执行
Floor Seven. Executive.
导演
Director.
O'Brien主任这位是Charlie Heller.
Director O'Brien, this is Charlie Heller.
-嗨.-你好，查理.请坐
- Hi. - Hello, Charlie. Come have a seat.
我宁愿不要
I'd rather not.
海勒先生，恐怕伦敦出了点状况
Mr. Heller, I'm afraid there was a situation in London.
你听说了吗？
Have you heard?
伦敦？
London?
克里斯托弗街酒店的袭击
An attack at the Christopher Street Hotel.
-查理...不，不.
- Charlie... - No, no.
非常抱歉，海勒先生
I'm very sorry, Mr. Heller.
什么？
What?
-你妻子被杀了.-没有.
- Your wife has been killed. - No.
不，她在开会
No, she's at a conference.
我们应该打电话给她
We should call her.
-查理，我很抱歉给你这个...-我们可以打电话给她吗？
- Charlie, I'm very sorry to give you this... - Can we call her?
我得给她打电话.
I have to call her.
查理，我想你需要看看这个
Charlie, I think you need to see this.
我们关注的是伦敦的突发新闻...
We're following a breaking news story here in London...
发生了可怕的人质事件...
where a terrifying hostage situation unfolded...
今天早些时候在克里斯托弗街酒店
at the Christopher Street Hotel earlier today.
四名袭击者冲进酒店，
Four assailants stormed into the hotel,
劫持了一些人质
taking a number of individuals hostage.
两个人不幸失去了生命...
Two individuals sadly lost their lives...
包括一个美国女人...
including an American woman...
-在磨难中被扣为人质的人.-没说是她.
- who was taken hostage during the ordeal. - It doesn't say it's her.
-目击者报告现场一片混乱...-查理，你必须相信我们.
- Eyewitnesses report a chaotic scene... - Charlie, you have to believe us.
.. 在酒店里，肇事者强行闯入...
...inside the hotel as the perpetrators forced their way...
这是我们从监控录像中调出的录像.
This is footage we pulled from surveillance cams.
恐吓客人和工作人员.
...terrorized the guests and the staff.
其中一名受害者已被确认
One of the victims has been identified.
她是一个32岁的美国女人
She is a 32-year-old American woman...
不幸被袭击者劫持为人质
that was tragically taken hostage by the assailants.
警方没有透露她
The police are not revealing her.
没关系.
It's all right.
我知道了.别担心.
I got this. Don't worry about it.
查理，查理，等等!
Charlie, Charlie, wait!
查尔斯!查尔斯!
Charles! Charles!
大都会警察已开始在全市范围内进行搜捕
Metropolitan Police has initiated a citywide manhunt.
他们正在不知疲倦地寻找袭击者...
They are working tirelessly to locate the assailants...
确保人质获救和获释...
and secure the rescue and release of the hostage...
我们怎么能不知道更多呢？
How can we not know more?
这是在伦敦…
This was in London...
947,000摄像头
947,000 cameras.
他们开车进入交通
They drove into traffic.
没有人能逃脱
Nobody is getting away with this.
我向你保证.
You have my word.
好的.
Okay.
告诉我我们目前所知道的
Tell me what we know so far.
海勒先生...
Mr. Heller...
恕我直言，让我们处理这件事
with respect, let us handle this.
原谅我，先生，我不相信我们正式见过面
Forgive me, sir, I don't believe we've officially met.
我是那个确保做这件事的人
I'm the one who's gonna ensure that those who did this
被追究责任
are held to account.
先生，恕我直言，那会是什么样子...
And what would that look like, sir, with respect...
被 “追究责任”？
being "held to account"?
听着，我们还不能详细说明
Look, we can't get into specifics yet.
当然，你明白这一点
Of course, you understand that.
我们会尽快告诉你我们能做什么
We'll tell you what we can as soon as we can.
你刚刚说了他说的话，只是更好
You just said what he said, only nicer.
回家吧，查理
Go home, Charlie.
你需要一些时间
You need to take some time.
-近亲？-是的.
- Next of kin? - Yes.
嫌疑人通过服务入口到达
The suspects arrived via the service entrance
大约11:00小时
around 11:00 hours.
车辆在一夜之间被盗
The vehicle had been stolen overnight
在东端大约01:24
at about 01:24 in the East End.
指纹，脱氧核糖核酸，都是专业擦洗出来的
Prints, DNA, all professionally scrubbed out.
四人小组
Four-person team.
看来他们开了个会...
Appears they had a meeting...
印尼的影响力投资在我们的雷达上
with Impact Investments out of Indonesia on our radar.
这就是一切开始的时候
This is when it all started.
里面一定有什么东西被加热了，
Something must have got heated inside,
它溢出到走廊里
it spilled out into the corridor.
Impact的安全细节变得神经质，
Impact's security detail got jumpy,
四个人中的一个吸引了他
and one of the four drew on him.
一个死亡，一个关键
One dead, one critical.
酒店保安已收到警报，并已报警
Hotel security are alerted, and the police have been called.
嫌犯现在正在竞相离开大楼...
The suspects are now in a race to leave the building...
他们决定买些保险
and they decided to grab some insurance.
所有人!趴下!
Everyone! Get down!
所有人都下来.
Everyone down.
趴下.趴下.
Get down. Get down.
不，不，不 快跑 快跑
No, no, no. Run. Run.
他们带走莎拉只是因为她想救别人
They only took Sarah because she tried to save someone else.
你按我说的做
You do as I say.
快走!
Move!
你按我说的做 快走!
You do as I say. Move!
带走Sarah的人是Mishka Blazhic.
The man who took Sarah is Mishka Blazhic.
起源于白俄罗斯，尽管通常位于莫斯科
Origins in Belarus, though often based in Moscow.
他们带着三名人质逃离了会议室
They fled the conference room with three hostages.
趴下，否则我开枪打你!
Stay down, or I'll shoot you!
这个人，劳伦斯·埃利什，是南非人
This man, Lawrence Ellish, is South African.
前特种部队
Ex-special forces.
Ellish似乎为更广泛的群体处理货物
Ellish seems to handle shipments for the wider group.
武装警察和保安从圣潘克拉斯车站赶来...
Armed police and security were arriving from St. Pancras Station...
但因为人质被命令退缩
but were ordered to hold back because of the hostages.
警察封锁了该地区，神枪手就位...
Police sealed off the area, marksmen in position...
但是嫌疑犯暴露了，他们知道
but the suspects are exposed, and they knew it.
-武装警察!放下武器!趴下!
- Armed police! Drop your weapons! - Get down!
莎拉的凶手更难追踪
Sarah's killer is harder to track.
他似乎感觉到了摄像机 他什么也没说
He seems to sense the cameras. He says nothing.
但是我处理了所有的闭路电视，手机...
But I processed all the CCTV, cell phones...
行车记录仪，车身凸轮...
dash cams, body cams...
和音频给我们一个360
and the audio to give us a 360.
这为我们提供了身份证
And that provides us with an ID.
这是Horst Schiller.
This is Horst Schiller.
与数十个mercs和国防团体的松散联系
Loose affiliations with dozens of mercs and defense groups.
我还在填写
I'm still filling that in.
他们似乎是作为接口操作...
They seem to be operating as interface...
在不良的国家行为者和恐怖主义实体之间
between bad state actors and terrorist entities.
所有的生意
All business.
他们继续被雇用
And they keep getting hired.
但对于这一个，我有一个当前位置
But for this one, I have a current location.
格雷琴·弗兰克.
Gretchen Frank.
前亚美尼亚人
Former Armenian IO.
她在巴黎.
She's in Paris.
在这家咖啡馆给她买面包
Buys her bread at this cafe.
经常出现在那里
Turns up there regularly.
你知道这个？
You knew this?
谢谢
Thank you.
-我们来比较一下.等等.
- We'll do a comparison. - Wait.
你已经知道格雷琴·弗兰克的事了？
You already know about Gretchen Frank?
我知道你想看到进步，查理
I understand you wanna see progress, Charlie.
但有时候，最好的做法是...
But sometimes, the best course of action...
并不总是最明显的
isn't always the most obvious.
“最明显”？
"Most obvious"?
我们想要整个网络
We want the whole network.
网络与莎拉无关
The network has nothing to do with Sarah.
但是一切都与主权有关
But everything to do with the sovereignty
和这个国家的安全
and security of this country.
你的所作所为对我们的所作所为非常重要，查理
What you do is very important to what we do, Charlie.
我们认为见到加里森博士对您有好处
We think it would be good for you to see Dr. Garrison.
我来这里是为了我自己还是机构？
Am I here for me or the Agency?
重要的是，我们评估您是否足够健康，可以重返工作岗位
It is important we assess you're well enough to return to work.
很明显.
Obviously.
但是你遭受了可怕的损失
But you've suffered a terrible loss.
我们想支持你
And we want to support you.
你能描述一下你的感受吗？
Can you describe your feelings?
现在？
Right now?
你是说，否认，愤怒...
You mean, denial, anger...
接受...
acceptance...
说更多
Say more.
她走了.
She's gone.
是的，她必须这样走
Yeah, that she had to go like that.
她打电话时我没有和她通电话
And that I didn't speak to her on the phone when she called.
-你为此责怪自己？-是的.
- And you blame yourself for that? - Yes.
她让我去的时候没有和她一起去，
For not going with her when she asked me to,
因为我从来没有
because I never do.
从来没有
Never did.
那让你有什么感觉？
And what is that making you feel?
很没用
Pretty useless.
生气了.
Angry.
非常非常生气
Very, very angry.
我给了局里杀害莎拉的凶手的名字
I gave the Agency the names of Sarah's killers.
他们什么也没做
They did nothing.
-你想让他们做什么？-他们的工作!
- What do you want them to do? - Their job!
我要他们去追杀莎拉的凶手
I want them to go after Sarah's killers.
这会让你感觉好些吗？
Will that make you feel better?
这不应该是关于我的
This shouldn't be about me.
莎拉很重要
Sarah mattered.
她应该得到更多
She deserves more.
但归根结底，这是关于你的
But in the end, this is about you.
莎拉走了.
Sarah's gone.
你必须试着接受这一点
You are gonna have to try and come to terms with that.
我可以帮忙.
I can help.
但只有你能真正让事情变得更好
But only you can really make things better.
楼层减五 解密和分析
Floor Minus Five. Decryption and Analysis.
装修时间表呢？
And the renovation schedule?
我们可以讨论密码学项目
We can discuss the cryptography project.
好吧.我能做到.
Okay. All right. I can do this.
谢谢 我想我们需要标记这个
Thanks. I think we need to flag this.
你最近一直很安静
You've been very quiet lately.
猜到我住在哪里了吗？
Guessed where I live yet?
你能在这里呆一会儿吗，伙计？
You good here for a minute, buddy?
我得把后门关上.
I gotta close up the back.
哦，是的.是啊.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
我把你掩护在这里
I got you covered out here.
七楼 执行
Floor Seven. Executive.
我拿着超过100只眼睛的电缆的亮点
I'm holding the highlights of over 100 eyes-only cables.
这些是从喀布尔站的数据缓存中双重编码的
These are double coded from a data cache out of Kabul Station.
这些是官方电报
These are the official cables.
相同的日期，相同的事件...
Same dates, same events...
除了非常关键的信息...
except for very key information...
已被更改或完全从记录中删除
that has been altered or completely scrubbed from the record.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
这是你的掩饰
This is your cover-up.
你疯了吗？
Have you lost your mind?
委婉地说
To put it mildly.
这是你摧毁叙利亚一家医院的行动命令
This is your order of operations to destroy a hospital in Syria.
在也门的盟军基地
An allied base in Yemen.
阿富汗政客的房子
An Afghani politician's house.
你不知道...
You have no idea what...
索马里的过境点
A border crossing in Somalia.
我统计了1,000多人伤亡...
I count more than 1,000 casualties...
超过400名平民死亡
and over 400 civilian fatalities.
只是出于对你最近损失的尊重...
It's only out of respect for your recent loss...
我不会把你赶出这个办公室
that I'm not throwing you out of this office.
我只想告诉你，你一点头绪都没有
I'm just gonna tell you, you don't have a goddamn clue.
你看到了吗？
You see right here?
车队？
The convoy?
你瞄准了我们的盟友
You targeted our allies.
你给它加了假标记
You false-flagged it.
你让他们都被解雇了...
You got them all fired up...
然后把它们吸回你想要的地方
and then sucked them right back in where you wanted them.
你在强迫任务爬行
You were forcing mission creep.
好了够了.
Okay. That's enough.
"够了"？
"That's enough"?
这些不是操作选择
These were not operational choices.
先生，你做出了政治决定
You, sir, made political decisions.
这些上面都是你的签名
And your signatures are all over these.
这里和这里 还有这里.
Here and here. And here.
-你远远高于你的工资等级 -还有这里.
- You are so far above your pay grade. - And here.
你说得对.你说得对.
Well, you're right. You're right.
也许我们应该...
Maybe we should...
把这个和导演联系起来？
take this up with the director?
让她打电话吗？
Let her call it?
也许是为了《泰晤士报》或《邮报》
Or maybe it's for the Times or the Post.
你带着这个去过媒体吗？
You've been to the press with this?
-你会进监狱的，白痴.也许吧.
- You'll go to jail, idiot. - Maybe.
但我们都会在一起
But we'll all be there together.
我们在这里有一个任务
We have a mission here.
一个责任
A responsibility.
我们将不惜一切手段保卫我们的国家
We'll defend our nation by any means necessary.
我不认为海勒先生来这里是为了辩论道德和实践，对吗？
I don't think Mr. Heller came here to debate ethics and practices, right?
没错.
Right.
首先，你要知道我设置了一个死人开关
First, you need to know that I've set up a dead man's switch.
如果我每五个小时不编码...
If I don't code in every five hours...
这些文件将自动发送
these files will automatically be sent
三位顶级调查记者...
to three top investigative journalists...
以及事件的详细报告和时间表
along with a detailed report and timeline of the events.
24小时后，这些文件将向公众发布
Twenty-four hours later, the files will be released to the public.
我明白了.
I get it.
我们杀了你，沃尔夫·布利策赢得艾美奖
We kill you, Wolf Blitzer wins an Emmy.
不，不只是杀了我
No. Not just kill me.
你把我关进监狱，你黑了我，你引渡了我...
You put me in jail, you black-site me, you extradite me...
你只会谴责自己
you'll only condemn yourselves.
那你到底想要什么？
Then what the hell do you want?
他想让我们杀了杀他妻子的人
He wants us to kill the people who killed his wife.
不，不.
No. No.
我不想让你杀了他们
I don't want you to kill them.
我想亲手杀了他们.
I wanna kill them myself.
-你说什么？-你听到了.
- I beg your pardon? - You heard me.
我想找到并杀死谋杀我妻子的人
I want to find and kill the people who murdered my wife.
中情局会训练我的.
The CIA will train me.
我是说，这是个恶作剧，对吧？
I mean, this is a practical joke, right?
我不认为你能打败一个90岁的修女
I don't think you could beat a 90-year-old nun
在一场摔跤比赛中
in an arm-wrestling match.
真有趣.
That's funny.
幽默？
Humor?
我想要特定任务的训练...
I want mission-specific training...
以及公司掌握的关于这些人的所有信息
and all the information the company has on these people.
现金 还有一个新的身份 一个传奇.
Cash. And a new identity. A legend.
还有别的吗？
Anything else?
阿斯顿·马丁？
An Aston Martin?
也许是喷气背包？
A jet pack, maybe?
我想要一个战斗的机会
I want a fighting chance.
我们怎么知道他真的设置了死者的开关？
How do we know he really set up the dead man's switch?
我们没有.
We don't.
我们需要对此保密
We need to keep a lid on this.
没错.
Right.
所以，让我们一起玩...
So, let's play along...
直到我们确定
till we're sure.
什么？实际上训练他？
What? Actually train him?
它能做什么伤害？
What harm can it do?
可能是他自己退出的
Probably quit of his own accord.
同时，把帕克带到他身上
Meanwhile, get Park onto him.
真不敢相信我会这么做
I can't believe I'm doing this.
我们擦洗他的生活，直到找到开关
We scrub his life till we find the switch.
如果它存在
If it exists.
如果不是...
If it doesn't...
也许有训练事故
well, maybe there's a training accident.
让我们用亨德森
Let's use Henderson.
护送队，在四号登机口等待新的到来
Escort team, stand by for new arrival at gate four.
查尔斯·海勒？
Charles Heller?
查理
Charlie.
你迟到了.
You're late.
恕我直言，我实际上是...
With respect, I'm actually about...
你迟到了.
You're late.
你来吗？
You comin'?
你在干什么？
The hell you doin'?
我不是Uber司机
I'm not an Uber driver.
对不起.
Sorry.
-好的.-把它放在左边.
- Okay. - Put it over here on the left.
是的 把那两个路由器放在那边
Yeah. Put those two routers over there.
-我拿到了.-HDMI电缆在包装盒中
- I got 'em. - The HDMI cables are in the box.
我打赌他是在虚张声势.
My bet is he's bluffing.
这个人的智商为170 我们不要假设
The man has an IQ of 170. Let's not assume.
唯一的出路是通过安全...
The only way out is through security...
他不可能带着数字文件通过他们
and there's not a chance he got past them with a digital file.
那他为什么在盲点站了40多分钟？
Then why is he standing in blind spots for over 40 minutes?
这里，这里，还有这里 在这一天
Here, here, and here. On this day.
看看那汗水
And look at that sweat.
是的 那是很大的汗水
Yeah. That is a lot of sweat.
你是我的经理吗？
Are you my handler?
我是亨德森上校.
I am Colonel Henderson.
我的朋友都叫我Hendo.
My friends call me Hendo.
你可以叫我亨德森上校.
You will call me Colonel Henderson.
我被要求给你一个进修课程...
I have been asked to give you a refresher course...
即使你在这里学到的
even though what you'll learn here
在正常课程之外
is outside the normal curriculum.
在全能的上帝旁边，我是世界上最重要的人...
Next to God Almighty, I am the most important person in the world...
一个寻找敌方战斗人员的特工
to an operative looking to target enemy combatants.
按照我说的做...
Do precisely as I say...
你有可能活着走出困境
and there is a slight chance you may come out of this alive.
只有一点点机会？
Only a slight chance?
我高估了你的几率来增强你的信心，孩子
I'm overestimating your odds to boost your confidence, son.
女士们先生们，请给我们房间
Ladies and gentlemen, please give us the room.
去喝杯咖啡吧.现在
Go have coffee. Now.
-是的，一定要检查所有的斑点 -好吧，检查一下
- Yeah, make sure you check for all spots. - All right, checking.
打开所有硬盘驱动器清洁器
Open all hard drive cleaners.
也带上支架
Bring the mountings too.
等等 你认为他用了撇渣器？
Wait. You think he used a skimmer?
他们不在这些驱动器上工作
They don't work on these drives.
他们在打印机上工作
They work on printers.
六天前，他把文件发给了打印机...
Six days ago, he sent the files to the printer...
用磁条掠过它们...
and skimmed them with a magnetic strip...
重写了打印机中的软件
rewrote the software in the printer.
并不意味着他把衣服从大楼里拿出来了
Doesn't mean he got the strip out of the building.
好吧 所以，ANPR在13号09:17的百思买有他的萨博汽车...
Okay. So, ANPR has his Saab at Best Buy at 09:17 on the 13th...
他在那里买了磁条
where he bought the magnetic strip.
然后有汽油
Then got gas.
在11:03复制文件...
Copied the files at 11:03...
第二天早上遇见了你们两个
met you two the next morning.
如果他走私出去，他就在这里做
If he smuggled it out, he did it here.
尽管如此，筛选器一无所获
Still, screener picked up nothing.
也许他吞下去了
Maybe he swallowed it.
仍然会捡起它
Still would have picked it up.
有点远
Kind of far.
你就站在那儿.
You stand right there.
别开枪!
Hold your fire!
试着靠近一点
Try it closer.
只是几个回合
Just a few rounds.
耶稣，玛丽和约瑟夫
Jesus, Mary, and Joseph.
我们测试一下你的愿景了吗？
Did we test your vision?
我想我只需要靠得那么近
Guess I just have to get that close.
是的，在空白范围内...
Yeah, at point blank range...
你可能有50-50的机会打出一些东西
you might have a 50-50 chance of hittin' something.
高估了我的赔率？
Overestimating my odds?
你们为什么不去楼下的浴室看看？
Why don't you guys check the downstairs bathroom?
把那些盒子递给我
Pass me those boxes.
所以，简易爆炸装置由一个启动器组成...
So, an IED consists of an initiator...
开关，主充...
switch, main charge...
电源，增强功能的容器
power source, container for enhancements.
像肥料，钉子之类的东西...
Stuff like fertilizer, nails...
玻璃，硝酸铵
glass, ammonia nitrate.
美是，你可以使用你所发现的，
Beauty is, you can use what you find,
大或小，如你所愿
big or small, as you like.
即兴发挥 为你的目的设计它
Improvise. Design it for your purpose.
随身携带组件
Carry the components with you.
我会被诅咒的
I'll be damned.
看来我们终于找到了你擅长的东西，海勒
Looks like we finally found something you do well, Heller.
我可以留着这个吗？
May I keep this?
当然可以.
Sure.
他来过这里两次 这个酒吧
He went here twice. This bar.
为什么？
Why?
24号晚上和多明格斯先生有一次
Once with Mr. Dominguez on the night of the 24th.
他妻子去世几周后
Couple of weeks after his wife died.
然后，下个月，13号
And then again, the next month, the 13th.
-他下载文件的那天.-对.
- The day he downloaded the files. - Right.
不过，我们搜查了它
We searched it, though.
让我们再次搜索它
Let's search it again.
名字？-克拉克·尼古拉斯·简森.
- Name? - Clark Nicholas Jenson.
给我拼一下.
Spell that for me.
J-E-N-S-O-N.
你确定？-是的.
- You sure? - Yeah.
不是简森·克拉克？
Not Jenson Clark?
不!-快点.
- No! - Fast.
克拉克·尼古拉斯·简森.
Clark Nicholas Jenson.
-你在哪里出生的？-罗利.北卡罗莱纳州罗利
- Where were you born? - Raleigh. Raleigh, North Carolina.
-哪家医院？现在!-杜克大学医院.
- Which hospital? Now! - Duke University Hospital.
-你母亲的娘家姓？-黛博拉·简·吊床.
- Your mother's maiden name? - Deborah Jane Hammock.
等一下.
Just a sec.
一切都被重新扫描了 甚至停车场
It's all being re-swept. Even the parking lot.
这里没有车
There's no drive here.
好吧 这就是我们没有找到的
Okay. That's what we didn't find.
但是我们发现了什么？
But what did we find?
我不知道，这是卡在点唱机下面的
I don't know, this was stuck under the jukebox.
给我25美分.
Give me a quarter.
拉动光盘
Pull the disc.
你...
You...
不是杀手.
are not a killer.
没有？
No?
-嘿，你是谁？-别管他们.
- Hey, who's this? - Leave them.
这些混蛋杀了你妻子，嗯？
These the assholes that killed your wife, huh?
那么，你打算怎么把它们都拿出来？
So, how do you plan to take them all out?
你杀的第一个，
The first one you kill,
你让其他人知道你要来
you let the other ones know you're coming.
然后呢？你有什么计划？
And then what? What's your plan?
你要怎么让兰利的人远离你？
How are you gonna keep the people at Langley off your ass?
这就是我需要你教我的
That's what I need you to teach me.
好吧.我来教你.
All right. I'll teach you.
拿去吧.
Take it.
别这样.-去吧，拿着.
- Come on. - Go on, take it.
什么事？你是什么...
What is it? What are you...
拿着!现在!嘿!
- Take it! Now! - Hey!
指着我的胸口
Point it at my chest.
-指向我的胸口!-你觉得...
- Point it at my chest! - You think that...
-现在就做!-好吧，好吧.
- Do it now! - All right, all right.
把你的手指放在扳机上!
Put your finger on the trigger!
来吧.
Come on.
看着我.
Look at me.
来吧.
Come on.
来吧，查理
Come on, Charlie.
瘫痪，不是吗？
Paralyzing, isn't it?
用活武器指着这样的人
Pointing a live weapon at someone like that.
你要么非常自信，要么非常愚蠢...
You have to either be very confident or very stupid...
这是它自己的一种信心
which is its own kind of confidence.
事实是你没有那种自信
Truth is you don't have that kinda confidence.
你也不傻.一点也不
And you are not stupid. Not in the slightest.
你不是杀手Charlie.
You're just not a killer, Charlie.
人们有一定的天赋
People have certain gifts.
你不能做我做的事，不管我怎么训练你...
You can't do what I do, no matter how much I train you...
尽管你不能教我如何破解密码
as much as you can't teach me how to break code.
我不能让你变成你不是的东西
I can't make you into somethin' that you're not.
对不起.
I'm sorry.
到时候...
When the time comes...
我来扣动扳机.
I'll pull the trigger.
到时候...
When the time comes...
你甚至不记得子弹是从枪的哪一端射出的
you won't even remember which end of the gun the bullet comes out of.
这要花多长时间？
How long is this gonna take?
有了这个加密，四五个小时
With this encryption, four or five hours.
如果她不能破解海勒的密码呢？
What if she can't break Heller's encryption?
她会的.
She will.
我们怎么知道他没有复印50份？
How do we know he didn't make 50 copies?
我们没有.
We don't.
阿里
Ali.
我们进去了.
We're in.
这是虚张声势
It's a bluff.
他在耍我们.
He was playing us.
他也做得很好
And he did pretty well, too.
让他离开董事会？
Take him off the board?
是啊.
Yeah.
好的.
Okay.
他走了？
He's gone?
他有一个装满护照的袋子...
He's got a bag full of passports...
甚至入侵了生物识别技术
even hacked the biometrics.
是的，他用看门人的卡出来了
Yeah, he got out on a janitor's card.
这是个笑话.
This is a joke.
也许你们都误判了这个人
Maybe y'all misjudged this individual.
你觉得呢？
You think?
他很清楚自己在做什么
He knew exactly what he was doin'.
让我们追逐面包屑足够长的时间...
Kept us chasin' breadcrumbs just long enough...
虽然他得到了一些训练
while he got himself some training.
海勒先生...
Mr. Heller...
窃听中情局官员...
bugging a CIA officer...
是叛国.
is treason.
女士们先生们，欢迎乘坐美国航空公司aa143航班...
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome aboard American Airlines flight AA143...
从华盛顿杜勒斯到伦敦希思罗机场的服务
with service from Washington Dulles to London Heathrow.
我们感谢您的关注，同时我们展示...
We thank you for your attention whilst we demonstrate...
飞机的安全特性
the safety features of the aircraft.
什么事？
Yes?
好吧，你可以打开它们
Okay, you can open them.
生日快乐.
Happy birthday.
它崩溃了吗？
Did it crash?
显然它没有被正确地绑住，被扔了...
Apparently it wasn't tied down properly and got thrown around...
龙卷风或飓风什么的
in a tornado or hurricane or something.
你觉得呢？
What do you think?
我无话可说
I have no words.
是吗？-是的.
-Yeah? - Yeah.
这不是疯了吗？
It's not crazy?
它需要一些工作
It needs some work.
你觉得呢？
You think?
这...
This...
这是我见过的最美的东西.
This is the most beautiful thing I've ever seen.
是吗？
Yeah?
是啊.
Yeah.
第二多
Second most.
生日快乐.
Happy birthday.
.. 巴黎现在将从第二站台出发
...Paris will be departing now from platform two.
他在伦敦.
He's in London.
他的一本护照在去巴黎的路上刚刚在移民局亮了起来
One of his passports just lit up at immigration on his way to Paris.
-我去找当地联络员.-没有.
- I'll grab local liaison. - No.
这个留在我们身边
This stays with us.
那Henderson呢？
What about Henderson?
给他打电话.
Call him.
嘿，那里，lockpick粉丝
Hey, there, lockpick fans.
好吧 今天我们要选一把公寓式的锁
Okay. Today we're gonna pick an apartment-style lock.
所以我们要做的第一件事
So, the first thing we're gonna do
你要拿着你的张力扳手...
is you're gonna take your tension wrench...
你要把它插在钥匙孔和插头的底部...
and you're gonna stick it in the bottom of the keyhole and the plug...
就像这样.感觉到了吗？
just like so. Feel it?
你只需要施加一点压力，就一点点
You're gonna apply just a little bit of pressure, just a little bit.
嘿，你不要太多
Hey, you don't want too much.
太多了，接下来会发生的是别针会绑在你身上...
Too much and what's gonna happen is the pins are gonna bind up on you...
而且您将无法将它们放在剪切线上
and you won't be able to get 'em up on a shear line.
你进不了那扇门.
And you're not gonna get into that door.
所以，轻轻地，轻轻地...
So, gently, gently...
感觉它来回旋转，仔细听
and feel it rotate back and forwards, listening carefully.
只是轻触
Just a light touch.
所有的针脚都会排成一行
All the pins are gonna line up.
然后，你进去了 给你.
And then, you're in. There you go.
如何开锁
How to pick a lock.
很简单
Pretty darn easy.
是的，别忘了喜欢和订阅
Yeah, don't forget to like and subscribe.
谢谢你们.下周见
Thank y'all. See you next week.
是的
Yes.
-向日葵.-是的.
- Sunflowers. - Yeah.
对不起.
Excuse me.
所有的，请
All of them, please.
百合花也请
The lilies as well, please.
我会把它们都拿出来
I'll get all of them.
你一定做了什么坏事
You must have done something really bad.
还没有.
Not yet.
是花粉.
It's pollen.
你是谁？
Who are you?
告诉我霍斯特·席勒在哪里，我会让你出去
Tell me where Horst Schiller is and I'll let you out.
去你的.
Screw you.
没有
No.
不，不，不，不.
No, no, no, no.
不，不，不 那没用的
No, no, no. That's not gonna work.
把门打开.
Open the door.
对不起.除非你告诉我.
I'm sorry. Not until you tell me.
拜托，告诉我他在哪里
Please, just tell me where he is.
为什么？
Why?
因为你杀了我妻子
Because you killed my wife.
她的名字叫莎拉
Her name was Sarah.
告诉我他在哪.
Tell me where he is.
告诉我!
Tell me!
我不...我不知道.
I don't... I don't know.
他联系...
He contacts...
他联系我们
He contacts us.
信使...
Messenger...
我听不见.
I can't hear you.
妈的!
Shit!
妈的.
Shit.
你好.
Hello.
37欧元，先生.
37 euros, please, sir.
我们对格雷琴·弗兰克了解多少？
What do we know about Gretchen Frank?
我们的人说她自己的人把她撞倒了
Our people say one of her own folks ran her down.
最有可能是伦敦工作南下时的后果
Most likely fallout from when the London job went south.
我会让州政府知道的
I'll let State know.
法国大使问
French ambassador is asking.
不是我们.
Wasn't us.
你要啤酒吗？
You want a beer?
是的 是啊，当然
Yeah. Yeah, sure.
你怎么找到我的？
How did you find me?
你给格雷琴·弗兰克打了电话
Phone you pulled off Gretchen Frank.
-就像雷达一样.-妈的.
- It's like a radar ping. - Shit.
不管你有多聪明
Doesn't matter how smart you are.
如果你惊慌失措，那总是会搞砸一个好计划
If you panic, that will always screw up a good plan.
然后是生存本能
Then there's the survival instinct.
没有人容易倒下
No one goes down easy.
当然，还有后果...
And, of course, the aftermath...
当你意识到你做了一些你永远无法撤消的事情
when you realize you've done something you can't undo, ever.
我可以忍受
I can live with that.
你不能.
You can't.
你让我吃惊，查理
You surprised me, Charlie.
我不能告诉你这是多么罕见
I can't tell you how rare that is.
但它在这里结束
But it ends here.
这项工作中没有三齐射致敬
There are no three-volley salutes in this work.
如果我们被发现，我们就是在垃圾箱里被发现的约翰
We're the John Does that get found in the dumpster, if we get found.
你不会的
Which you won't.
对不起.
I'm sorry.
不，那些是很好的教训
No, those were good lessons.
你是个好老师，Hendo.
You're a good teacher, Hendo.
我考虑到了这一点
I took that into account.
五十对五十的赔率，对吧？
Fifty-fifty odds, right?
你有没有考虑过我擅长的事情？
Did you ever account for the things I was good at?
在计时器上充电
Base charge on a timer.
你有一条新消息
You have one new message.
遇见奥斯曼货物
Meet Ottoman Cargo.
七号机库 他们在等你.
Hangar seven. They're expecting you.
你需要500欧元现金
You'll need 500 euros in cash.
你有一条新消息
You have one new message.
Fahri咖啡馆，kuvelo ğ lu街
The Fahri Cafe, Kuveloğlu Street.
我会递给你一本书
I will pass you a book.
等等 他不是你要找的人
Wait. He is not who you're looking for.
检查你的手机
Check your phone.
不管你出于什么原因，你来这里都是鲁莽的
It was reckless of you to come here, whatever your reasons.
听着，我需要你的帮助
Listen, I need your help.
不，你无处可去
No. You have nowhere else to go.
那不是一回事.
That's not the same thing.
我们在购物，好吗？
We're shopping, okay?
把你的背包给我.
Give me your backpack.
还有你的帽子.
And your hat.
现在你看起来不像美国人了
Now you look less American.
你想要什么？
What do you want?
我妻子被谋杀了
My wife was murdered.
我知道你妻子的事
I know about your wife.
巴黎是你吗？
And Paris, that was you?
我需要找到其他人
I need to find the others.
不，不在这里
No. Not here.
离这里四个街区有一个停车场，那边
There is a parking garage four blocks from here, that way.
一楼.
First floor.
去买点东西，然后半小时后在那里见我
Do some shopping, then meet me there in half an hour.
如果你没有被跟踪，我们再谈
And if you're not followed, we'll talk more.
你多久了？
So, how long has it been you?
六年了.
Six years.
我丈夫是中情局的线人.
My husband was a CIA asset.
前克格勃
Former KGB.
他一直在审讯，直到他去世
He was Inquiline until he died.
他从窗户掉了下来
He fell out of a window.
对不起.
I'm sorry.
从窗户意外坠落
Accidental falls from windows
是前克格勃的头号死因
are the number-one cause of death of former KGB.
你不知道？
You didn't know?
他教我他所做的一切...
He taught me everything he was doing...
如何挖掘数据缓存，加密文件
how to mine data cache, encrypt files.
他死后...
And after he died...
嗯，我决定保持和你部门的联系...
well, I decided to keep up my connection to your department...
以防我需要帮助
in case I needed help.
所以我一直以为你是个中年人.
Which is why I always thought you were a middle-aged man.
因为你是，首先
Because you were, to begin with.
你也不是我想象的那样
You aren't exactly what I pictured, either.
你是怎么想象我的？
How did you picture me?
我不知道.
I don't know.
我猜是中情局先生-带枪的人
Mr. CIA-man-with-a-gun, I guess.
你会帮我吗？
So, you'll help me?
它比任何警报系统都要好
It's better than any alarm system.
这是我住了一个多月的第一个地方...
This is the first place I've stayed in for more than a month...
在过去的三年里
in the last three years.
我不睡觉
I don't sleep.
但我只是不想再跑了
But I just don't want to run anymore.
你凭什么认为他们在这里找不到你？
What makes you think they won't find you here?
那天晚上...
For that night...
当他们这样做的时候
when they do.
你真的认为你会用这个击倒俄国人吗？
You really think you're gonna fight off the Russians with that?
不适合他们
It's not for them.
是给我的.
It's for me.
这是三个，对吗？
Those are the three, correct?
是啊.
Yeah.
席勒似乎是协调员
Schiller seems to be the coordinator.
主谋.
Ringleader.
但他也是最难描述的
But he's also the most difficult to profile.
据我所知，他们是扩散链中的中间人
As far as I can tell, they operate as middlemen in the proliferation chain.
就像你给我看的数据一样...
And just like the data you showed me...
他们还为摩尔导演的黑色行动寻找雇佣军
they also source mercenaries for Director Moore's black ops.
埃利什提供武器，但他超出了偏执狂
Ellish sources the weapons, but he's beyond paranoid.
所以，我们必须想办法把他从黑暗中拉出来
So, we have to find a way to pull him out of the dark.
好吧 也许我可以开始谈话了
Okay. Perhaps I can start the conversation.
建议我给他一份合同
Suggest I have a contract for him.
看看他是否会参与
See if he will engage.
好的这位是Mishka Blazhic.
Okay. And this is Mishka Blazhic.
他似乎住在莫斯科，但他喜欢继续前进
He seems to be based in Moscow, but he likes to keep on the move.
享受他的奢侈品 到处旅行头等舱
Enjoys his luxuries. Travels everywhere first class.
他可能是薄弱环节
He may be the weak link.
甚至在线发布
Even posts online.
这只是上周
This was just last week.
没有位置，但葡萄园在平地上...
No location, but the vineyard on level ground...
而且间距比典型的要宽，所以气候可能更热
and the spacing is wider than typical, so probably hotter climate.
白垩质土壤 也许是花岗岩
Chalky soil. Maybe granite.
低沉的太阳照在他酒杯里的酒上
Low sun hitting the wine in his glass.
但是葡萄园会是南北倾斜的...
But the vineyard would be angled north-south...
所以现在是日出
so it's sunrise.
还有这个教堂.建筑看起来像西班牙
And this church. The architecture looks Spanish.
所以，10月很热
So, hot in October.
也许是西班牙中部
Maybe central Spain.
在这里，在倒影中...
And here, in the reflection...
女朋友，也许吧
girlfriend, maybe.
她就在那儿.
And there she is.
亚历山德拉·索洛瓦亚，
Alexandra Solovoya,
谁也喜欢旅行
who also likes to travel.
上周，她乘飞机去了莫斯科马德里
And she flew Moscow to Madrid, last week.
我们需要投射使美国伟大的一切...
We need to project everything that makes America great...
但是我们需要公开地做...
but we need to do it openly...
透明地 -我们得假设他还活着.
- and transparently. - We have to assume he's still alive.
他有三个目标
He has three targets.
所以，我保证...
And so, I pledge...
我们需要找到并盯着他们所有人
We need to locate and get eyes on all of them.
.. 这个机构将值得国家的信任
...this agency will be worthy of the nation's trust.
在我们国家内外，我们将承担责任
Within our country and beyond, we will be accountable.
我看了你的演讲
I saw your speech.
太棒了.
It was excellent.
你知道吗，你是我前任第一个向我介绍的人？
You know, you're the first person my predecessor briefed me on?
关于你在ISIS上的混蛋，AQ...
About the stick up your ass on ISIS, AQ...
伊朗，反恐？
Iran, counterterrorism?
即使是现在，在强制退休三年后...
Even now, three years after mandatory retirement...
他们一直在寻找其他方式
they keep looking the other way.
但现在是家务时间...
But it's housekeeping time...
我需要知道你的立场
and I need to know where you stand.
听起来你是在暗示我该私了
Sounds like you're suggesting it's time for me to go private.
写一本关于我在公司的时间的书
Write a neat book about my time with the company.
然而，我们在这里，享受这美味的一餐
Yet here we are, enjoying this lovely meal.
那么，为什么？
So, why?
哦，拜托.
Oh, please.
我是新来的，但我不傻
I'm new, but I'm not stupid.
我需要你负责
I need you to be accountable.
对我来说.
To me.
别再在沙滩上玩你的黑棋了
Stop playing your black ops in the sand.
我需要跨越一切
I need to be across everything.
我的意思是一切
And I mean everything.
嘿，布莱恩？
Hey, Brian?
你能给我再拿一个这种酸面团卷吗？
Can you bring me another one of these sourdough roll thingies?
当然，摩尔先生
Sure, Mr. Moore.
我给你讲个故事.
I'll tell you a story.
你的前任让我坐在同一张桌子上...
Your predecessor sat me down at this very same table...
他任期不到一周...
no more than a week into his term...
给了我几乎完全相同的演讲
and gave me pretty much this exact same speech.
哦，等等.
Oh, wait.
也许是他的前任
Maybe it was his predecessor.
我不记得了.
I can't remember.
不管怎样，我会告诉你我对他们说了什么
Anyway, I'll tell you what I told them.
我全力支持你
You have my full support.
很好.
Good.
说得好.
Good talk.
享受意大利面
Enjoy that pasta.
在哪？
Where?
马德里
Madrid.
听谁的命令？
On whose orders?
你的午餐约会
Your lunch date.
让我们找个自己的人来玩吧
Let's get someone of our own in play.
找到他了.
Found him.
在Aguilar酒店.
At the Aguilar Hotel.
五颗星 夜总会.屋顶游泳池
Five stars. Nightclub. Rooftop pool.
什么？
What?
兰利也会找到他的
Langley will be onto him, too.
那我们继续追踪他...
Well, then we keep tracking him...
直到我们有一个明确的领域
until we have a clear field.
没有
No.
我要走了.
I'm going.
好的.
Okay.
留意他
And keep an eye out for him.
这就是他们要派的人
This is who they'll send.
干杯，干杯，干杯
Cheers, cheers, cheers.
没有人走路回家 我们滚回家
Nobody walks home. We roll home.
他是个夜间游泳者
He's a night swimmer.
他付钱给工作人员为他清理屋顶
He pays the staff to clear the rooftop for him.
.. 团队的批准...
...the approval of the team...
雄心勃勃的计划获得了绿灯
and the ambitious plans were given the green light.
天空池悬浮在70米的地面上方16层
The sky pool is suspended 16 stories above the ground which is 70 meters.
透明玻璃的总厚度将为420厘米...
The thickness of the clear glass will be 420 centimeters in total...
由三个带有气隙的面板制成，以提高强度
made of three panels with air gaps to improve the strength.
游泳池将3米高，5米宽...
The pool will be three meters tall, five meters wide...
可以容纳令人印象深刻的150吨水
and can hold an impressive 150 tons of water.
你可以从那里开枪打他
You could shoot him from there.
你没见过我开枪
You haven't seen me shoot.
我不能在这里说，老板，但为什么埋葬他？
Not for me to say here, boss, but why bury him?
为什么不把他卷起来？
Why not just roll him up?
我们已经过去了 太臭了
We're past that. Too big of a stench.
听着，他几乎发明了我们一半的监控技术
Look, he practically invented half of our surveillance tech.
现在，我会找到他...
Now, I will find him...
但是你手上可能会有更大的恶臭
but you might have a bigger stench on your hands
如果他再给我们一次失误
if he gives us the slip again.
你不会让这种事发生的.
You won't let that happen.
查理·海勒.
Charlie Heller.
好吧 你得告诉我
Okay. You're going to have to clue me in.
完整性
Integrity.
一切都与诚信有关
It's all about integrity.
有道德之类的吗？
To have morals, something like that?
是的 还有别的东西
Yeah. And something else as well.
如果我的数学是对的
If I have the math right.
我该走了.
I should move.
我可以确认游泳池将像往常一样准备好了吗？
Can I confirm the pool will be ready as usual?
在这里.
Over here.
第二个凳子在酒吧
Second stool down at the bar.
是的 他呢？
Yeah. What about him?
他一直在跟踪我
He's been following me.
我给他打了三次钟
I've clocked him three times.
是啊，好吧，哪里有一个，总会有更多
Yeah, well, where there's one, there's always more.
妈的.
Shit.
你说得对.
You're right.
是的，我抓到你的人了
Yeah, I've got your man.
他在大厅里，朝电梯那边走去
He's in the lobby, moving across towards the elevators.
酒吧里的那个人，我有他的身份证
And the man at the bar, I have an ID on him.
查理，他也是中情局的
Charlie, he's also CIA.
你现在必须离开
You have to leave now.
Heller你在听我说吗？
Heller, are you listening to me?
不，不，我们按计划去
No. No, we go as planned.
我被允许使用游泳池
I'm allowed to use the pool.
我付了钱.
I paid for it.
有什么问题吗？
Is there a problem?
告诉我在哪里能找到霍斯特·席勒
Tell me where to find Horst Schiller.
你是谁？
Who are you?
你拿枪指着我妻子的头
You held a gun to my wife's head.
她吓坏了.
She was terrified.
-你找错人了.-是的，是的，我知道.
- You have the wrong guy. - Yeah, yeah, I know.
你没有扣动扳机
You didn't pull the trigger.
告诉我在哪里能找到他
So, tell me where to find him.
如果这是一个笑话，我不明白
If this is a joke, I don't get it.
这不是开玩笑.
It's not a joke.
这是一个控制设备的遥控器...
This is a remote that controls a device...
这一直在给你下面的玻璃片之间的空气减压
that's been decompressing the air between the sheets of glass beneath you.
如果我触发它，玻璃就会碎
If I trigger it, the glass will shatter.
告诉我他在哪...
So, tell me where he is...
或者游得很快
or swim very fast.
你找错人了
You have the wrong person.
没有
No.
我有正确的人
I have exactly the right person.
查理，你应该离开那里
Charlie, you should get out of there.
妈的.
Shit.
亨德森朝你的方向去了
Henderson's headed your way.
走向楼梯间
Go towards the stairwell.
他现在在哪里？
Where is he now?
他在楼梯间.上面三层
He's in the stairwell. Three floors above.
走向地下室
Head towards the basement.
后面有个出口.
There's an exit in the back.
妈的!还有一个...
Shit! There's another one...
已经在地下室了.
already in the basement.
他朝你走来
He's coming towards you.
哪条路？哪条路？
Which way? Which way?
向左 向左走
Left. Go left.
他在哪里？另一个？
Where is he? The other one?
我不知道.我正在找.
I don't know. I'm looking right now.
Heller住手!
Heller, stop!
停下
Stop! Stop.
查理，你得离开那里
Charlie, you gotta get out of there.
你得走了.
You've got to go.
现在.
Right now.
你想见我？
You wanted to see me?
请坐.
Have a seat.
Charlie Heller在哪？
Where's Charlie Heller?
据我所知，还在休丧假
As far as I know, still on bereavement leave.
你和他谈过了吗？
You talk to him at all?
我们认为现在最好给他一些空间
We thought it best to give him some space for now.
有道理.
Makes sense.
如果我们有他的消息，我会告诉你的
I'll let you know if we hear from him.
在那里
There.
看到了吗？-是的.他在干什么？
- See that? - Yeah. What's he doing?
他的嘴唇在动
His lips are moving.
看看他的耳朵.
Look in his ear.
他在和某人说话
He's talking to somebody.
谁？
Who?
酒店保安昨天被黑了
Hotel security was hacked yesterday.
没错 时间到了
Right. Time?
11:07 这是一份职业
11:07. It was a pro job.
起源充其量是模糊的
The origination is murky at best.
也许是伊斯坦布尔
Istanbul, perhaps.
跟我说话.
Talk to me.
海勒的
From Heller.
“如果我不得不猜测，你是一个50岁的俄罗斯人...
"If I had to guess, you're a 50-year-old Russian man...
“住在伊斯坦布尔”
living in Istanbul."
"Inquiline."
代号 “Inquiline”
Code name "Inquiline."
找到这个人
Locate this person.
你感觉如何？
How are you feeling?
我不知道.这次我没搞砸这么多
I don't know. I didn't screw up so much this time.
不太确定这是件好事，对吧？
Not so sure that's a good thing, right?
实际上，我是说喂鸟
Actually, I meant feeding the birds.
当我丈夫被谋杀时...
When my husband was murdered...
我没有准备好面对这个世界会变得多么安静
I wasn't prepared for how quiet the world would become.
一个人在你生活中发出的所有声音
All the sounds that a person makes in your life.
节奏
The rhythms.
你如何在一天中的某个时间期待某种声音
How you expect a certain sound at a certain time of day.
门，脚步声
The door, footfall.
他过去做的愚蠢的事情让我很恼火
The stupid thing he used to do that annoyed me.
然后突然...
And then suddenly there's...
没什么.
nothing.
太棒了...
It's just great...
安静.
silence.
对我来说...
For me...
从那以后的每一刻都是关于...
every moment since has been about...
试图填补这种沉默
trying to fill that silence.
你需要问问你自己...
You need to ask yourself...
做这一切...
Doing all this...
你应该如何填补你的？
is it how you should fill yours?
代号，查询
Code name, Inquiline.
前FSB通过克格勃
Ex-FSB by way of the KGB.
04年向我们翻转
Flipped to us in '04.
-17年去世.死者？
- Deceased in '17. - Deceased?
俄国人怀疑他的遗孀可能在他的地方活动
The Russians suspect his widow may be operating in his place.
给我找伊斯坦布尔的俄罗斯站长
Get me the Russian station chief in Istanbul.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
我不想要你的任何东西
I want nothing from you.
我只想和另一个人在我身边睡一晚
I just want to sleep for one night with another person beside me.
好的.
Okay.
妈的.
Shit.
-快走.-妈的.
- Move. - Shit.
走吧 快走，快走
Go. Move, move.
这边走.这边走.来吧.
This way. This way. Come on.
来吧.来吧.
Come on. Come on.
嘿.
Hey.
他们走了吗？
Have they gone?
没事的.没事的.
It's okay. It's okay.
我们没事.我们失去了他们
We're okay. We've lost them.
我们没事，我们没事，我们没事
We're okay, we're okay, we're okay.
妈的.
Shit.
你没事.
You're okay.
妈的.
Shit.
哦，天哪.
Oh, God.
-海勒在柏林.什么？
- Heller's in Berlin. - What?
这是40分钟前的事了.
This was 40 minutes ago.
是吗？
Yeah?
把钱放在椅子上 数一数.
Put the money on the chair. Count it.
直到我检查硬件
Nothing until I inspect the hardware.
硬件就在那里 说吧.
Hardware's right there. Go ahead.
别挂电话.
Stay on the phone.
妈的.
Shit.
你刚刚武装了一个简易爆炸装置 它在光束触发器上
You just armed an IED. It's on a beam trigger.
你放下盖子，移开，或者穿过光束，它就会引爆
You drop the lid, move away, or cross the beam, it detonates.
你到底是谁？
Who the hell are you?
你真的认为我是一个人来的吗？
Do you honestly think I came here alone?
看这张照片
Look at the photograph.
看到了吗？
See it?
你看到了吗？
Do you see it?
是啊，当然.我看到照片了
Yeah, sure. I see the photograph.
你认识她吗？
Do you recognize her?
也许是伦敦？
London, maybe?
那是莎拉.
That's Sarah.
你夺走了她的生命.
You took her life.
没有理由
For no reason.
不是我，好吗？
Wasn't me, okay?
我没有开枪打她
I didn't shoot her.
好吧.
Fine.
告诉我我需要知道的，我会关闭设备
Just tell me what I need to know, and I'll deactivate the device.
好吧.好的.快点，快点.
All right. Okay. Come on, come on.
他在哪里？席勒 他在哪里？
Where is he? Schiller. Where is he?
这是不可能的，伙计
It's impossible, man.
在Gretchen和Blazhic的事之后他走了.
After what happened to Gretchen and Blazhic, he's gone.
Horst走了.
Horst's gone.
那你对我没用了...
Well, then you are of no use to me...
是吗？-不，不，不，等等，等等，等等!
- are you? - No, no, no. Wait, wait, wait!
他会在海上，对吧？他留在他的船上
He'll be at sea, right? He stays on his boat.
-哪个海？我不知道.俄罗斯水域
- Which sea? - I don't know. Russian waters.
那是25,000英里的海岸线
That's 25,000 miles of coastline.
-哪个海？我不知道!俄罗斯水域!
- Which sea? - I don't know! Russian waters!
不够好.太含糊了.
Not good enough. Too vague.
哦，来吧，伙计!
Oh, come on, man!
你给他提供这些东西，对吗？这些导弹
You supply him with this shit, right? These missiles.
对吗？-是的.
- Correct? - Yeah.
是吗？你把它们送到哪里？
Yeah? So where do you deliver them?
波罗的海滨海边疆区的一个港口
A port on the Baltic Primorsk.
就在那里.好吧，有一个...
It's there. Okay, there's a...
有一个咖啡馆
There's a café.
他在那里打电话，就是这样
He calls in there, and that's it.
你怎么联系他？
How do you contact him?
他用两个数字给他的人
He uses two numbers for his men.
如果他们得到正确的代码，他们知道是我
If they get the right codes, they know it's me.
我只有这些了.
That's all I have.
我们会看到的
We'll see.
把你的电话给我.
Give me your phone.
你的电话.
Your phone.
数字在那里
The numbers are there.
密码是他们的名字
The codes are by their names.
他们的名字？
Their names?
Simon和Kristoff.
Simon and Kristoff.
我没有搞砸，伙计 Simon和Kristoff.来吧.
I'm not messing, man. Simon and Kristoff. Come on.
-在那里.看到了吗？看，我不是...你说得对.
- There. You see? See, I'm not... - You're right.
我没撒谎.现在，关掉这个东西
I'm not lying. Now, deactivate this thing.
嘿，你要去哪里？
Hey, where are you going?
你要去哪里？
Where you going?
如果你跳得很快，你可能会在爆炸中幸存下来
If you jump really fast, you might survive the blast.
求你了!
Please!
等等!
Wait!
我们在罗马有一个ping
We got a ping in Rome.
那个小混蛋现在在博物馆里？
The little prick is now at a museum?
他不在罗马
He's not in Rome.
我们在追逐蒸汽
We're chasing vapors.
怎么做？
How?
因为他们在铲掉劳伦斯·埃利什先生剩下的东西...
Because they're shoveling what's left of Mister Lawrence Ellish...
在罗马尼亚的泥泞中
out of the mud in Romania.
他刚在布拉格上了电车
He just got on a tram in Prague.
你需要再次睡觉
You need to sleep again.
你在开玩笑吗？
Are you kidding me?
你觉得怎么样，伙计？
What do you think, man?
只是巧合还是什么？
Just coincidence or what?
是的，不知何故，我对此表示怀疑
Yeah, somehow, I doubt that.
你说呢，也许...
What do you say, maybe...
我们去拿杯低劣的俄罗斯咖啡，嗯？
let's go get us a cup of shitty Russian coffee, huh?
来吧.
Come on.
看看你在这个又大又坏的城市
Look at you in the big, bad city.
来吧，我们走.
Come on, let's go.
所以，一只逃跑的兔子，嗯？
So, a rabbit on the run, huh?
坐下，伙计
Sit down, man.
所以你是来杀我的？
So, you're here to kill me?
不，那不是我真正做的
Nah, that's not really what I do.
我是说，我可能会让你被杀 你知道，促进它
I mean, I might set you up to get killed. You know, facilitate it.
你在找什么？
What are you looking for?
我不知道，我的刺客？
I don't know, my assassin?
你的刺客？是啊，你觉得呢？
Your assassin? Yeah, and what do you think?
刺客长什么样？
What does an assassin look like?
我是说，可能是任何人，嗯？
I mean, it can kinda be anyone, huh?
我是说，即使是一个小小的书呆子也喜欢在电脑上工作
I mean, even a slight little nerdy fella likes to work on computers.
他唯一危险的是...
Only thing dangerous about him is...
他有一个关于修复塞斯纳的梦想...
he's got this dream about rehabbing a Cessna...
只是为了向自己证明他不害怕
just to fly it around to prove to himself that he's not afraid.
顺便说一下，这些是杀手
These are killer, by the way.
我要给你看点东西.
I'm gonna show you something.
我得把它交给你 我差点没认出你来.
I gotta hand it to you. I almost didn't recognize you.
我对团队说，“不，不可能 那不是他 ”
I said to the team, "Nah, there's no way. That ain't him."
你想要什么？
What do you want?
老实说...
Honestly...
只是来救你的命
just here to save your life.
你要怎么做？
How are you gonna do that?
Chuck你杀了三个人.
Chuck, you killed three people.
你说完了吗？你受够了吗？
Are you done? Have you had enough?
不，我要扣动扳机的人 我都想要.
No. I want the guy who pulled the trigger. I want 'em all.
该死，伙计
Damn, dude.
嗯，那是相当冷血的
Well, that's pretty cold-blooded.
你觉得他们会让你离开俄罗斯吗？
You think they're gonna let you leave Russia?
我是说，这到底是怎么回事？你怎么离开这里？
I mean, how does that even work? How do you leave here?
你离开这里的唯一方法是在一个盒子里
The only way you leave here is in a box.
但是如果你现在和我一起离开这里，我可以帮你
But if you walk out of here right now with me, I can help you.
没人派我来.我一个人在这里
Nobody sent me. I'm here on my own.
妈的，也许你在这个领域有前途
Shit, maybe you got a future in this field.
也许我们可以想出这样的办法，嗯？
Maybe we can figure something out like that, huh?
跟我回家吧.
Just come home with me.
我在外地有前途吗？
I have a future in the field?
嗯，我可以发誓你刚才说我没有未来
Well, I could have sworn you just said I have no future.
听着，我不会坐在这里假装我明白你的所作所为
Look, I'm not gonna sit here and pretend like I understand what's goin' on with you.
我不知道，好吗？我从未有过这种感觉
I don't, okay? I've never felt that.
你的损失，我明白了
Your loss, I get it.
但你尊敬她
But you honored her.
你觉得她想要什么？
What do you think she wants?
你认为她想让你和这些人一起死在这个国家吗？
You think she wants you to die here in this country with these people?
她会希望你回家的，伙计
She would want you home, man.
没有
No.
我不能回家.
I can't go home.
为什么？
Why?
她不在那里.
She's not there.
好的.
Okay.
你现在把头转起来，好吗，查克？
You keep your head on a swivel now, okay, Chuck?
先生，对不起
Sir, I'm sorry.
你会说英语吗？
Do you speak English?
对不起，先生 对不起
Sorry, sir. I'm sorry.
有两个人.
There were two men.
和你在卡车上
With you on a truck.
不是很令人印象深刻，是吗？
It's not very impressive, is it?
放在舱口下的货物附近？
Placed near the cargo you have below those hatches?
我想我甚至可能觉得有点被侮辱了
I think I might even feel a little insulted.
-谁在追我？-我.
- Who's coming after me? - Me.
我 我在追你
Me. I'm coming after you.
谁在管理你？
And who is running you?
什么，你害怕摩尔主任最终决定退出吗？
What, are you afraid Director Moore has finally decided to call it quits?
你关机了吗？
Have you shut down?
不管你认为你知道什么...
Whatever you think you know...
我知道摩尔和凯勒雇了你和你的衣服...
I know Moore and Caleb hire you and your outfit...
为他们进行秘密行动 我有证据.
to carry out black ops for them. I have proof.
但是... 这不是问题所在，是吗？
But... that's not what this is about, is it?
没有
No.
我来这里是为了面对杀害我妻子的凶手
I came here to face my wife's killer.
看着他的眼睛
To look him in the eyes.
告诉他她很重要
And tell him she mattered.
莎拉很重要
Sarah mattered.
所以，只有你
So, it is just you.
Gretchen, Blazhic, Ellish...
他们派来抓你的人
the men that they sent after you.
整件事都是你的报复？
This whole thing is all your revenge?
查理的复仇？
Charlie's revenge?
求你了.
Please.
我记得你的妻子
I remember your wife.
她取代了别人的位置
She took the place of someone else.
非常非常勇敢
It's very, very brave.
我很抱歉她死了
I am sorry she died.
但那是...
But it was...
必要的
necessary.
警察封锁了我们的出口
The police had blocked our exit.
我必须证明如果他们不允许我们离开会发生什么
I had to demonstrate what would happen if they did not allow us to leave.
就这样？
That's it?
“必要”？
"Necessary"?
你对我来说没什么不同...
You are not so different to me...
杀死这些人是为了找到你来这里的路
killing these people to find your way here to me.
这让你感觉好些了吗？
Has it made you feel better?
要杀了你我才知道.
I won't know till I've killed you.
是...
It was...
-一瞬间.你的妻子.-不，不是.
- an instant. Your wife. - No, it wasn't.
然而你却折磨我的同事...
Yet you tortured my colleagues...
把一个人扔下16层楼...
dropped a man 16 stories...
把一个女人闷死在一个上锁的房间里
suffocated a woman in a locked chamber.
你让他们都手无寸铁
You had them all unarmed, defenseless.
从远处策划了你精心策划的谋杀
Staged your elaborate murders from a distance.
你知道为什么吗？
And you know why?
我知道.
I do.
因为很难近距离生活
Because it's hard to take a life up close.
你每次都会失去一些东西
You lose something each time.
你永远无法找回的自己
A piece of yourself you cannot get back ever.
你已经失去了很多
And you've lost so much already.
所以，你必须给他们一个逃脱老鼠陷阱的机会...
So, you had to give them a chance to escape the mouse trap...
跑得足够快
to run just fast enough.
因为那样你就可以告诉自己手上没有血迹
Because then you can tell yourself there's no blood on your hands.
但并不意味着你软弱
But doesn't mean you're weak.
只是意味着你不是真正的杀手
Just means you are not truly a killer.
不相信我？
Don't believe me?
说吧.
Go ahead.
你是来杀我的.拿去吧.你会看到的.
You're here to kill me. Take it. You'll see.
这不是诡计.给你.
It's not a trick. Here.
那好吧.
All right, then.
面对面地结束它
End it face to face.
我的一个朋友曾经告诉我，我永远无法扣动扳机
A friend of mine once told me I'd never be able to pull the trigger.
但他也说我永远不会杀人
But he also said I'd never be able to kill.
就是这样.
There it is.
这就是我来这里的目的
That's what I came here for.
平衡天平
To balance the scales.
让你感受到她那一刻的感受
To make you feel what she felt in that moment.
在你杀了她之前.
Before you killed her.
我带我们走了弯路
I've taken us on a detour.
胡说.
Bullshit.
我已经控制了你的船
I've taken control of your boat.
我们刚刚到达芬兰水域
We've just reached Finnish waters.
这是不可能的
That is not possible.
这艘船是个金库.
This ship is a vault.
你自己的中情局坚持要这么做
Your own CIA insisted upon it.
使用我写的加密
Using encryption I wrote.
听着，都是从我的酒店房间跑出来的
Look, it's all running from my hotel room.
这两个人可能打碎了我的手机，但他们抓住了他们的手机...
These two may have smashed my phone, but they held on to theirs...
还有我的手表.
and my watch.
所以，我是发射器，而你...
So, I'm the transmitter and you...
你邀请我进来的.
you invited me in.
我只需要你说话，只要把我们带到这里
I just needed you to talk as long as it took to get us here.
那将是芬兰海军和国际刑警组织
That would be the Finnish Navy and Interpol.
我给了他们这个位置
I gave them this location.
我们正在登上你的船
We are boarding your boat.
我们是按照国际法行事的
We are acting in accordance with international law.
你被逮捕了.
You are being placed under arrest.
退下，退下!
Stand down, stand down!
趴下
Down.
海勒.
Heller.
查理·海勒.
Charlie Heller.
当我担任这个角色时...
When I took up this role...
我向在这栋楼里工作的每个人都说清楚了...
I made it clear to everyone who works in this building...
即使我们的工作有时在黑暗的角落里进行...
that even though our work sometimes goes on in dark corners...
这不是借口...
that is no excuse...
让黑暗掩盖我们的目标或方法
to allow darkness to obscure our objectives or our methods.
所以，我非常难过地告诉你，信息已经浮出水面...
So, I'm deeply saddened to have to tell you that information has surfaced...
这牵涉到该机构的高级成员执行流氓任务...
that implicates senior members of this agency in carrying out rogue missions...
这使我们自己的运营商和代理商的安全面临巨大风险
which put the safety of our own operators and agents we work with at great risk.
先生们.
Gentlemen.
赢得战争的代价不能成为我们的荣誉
The cost of winning the war cannot be our honor.
这些行动没有受到制裁
Those operations were not sanctioned.
他们是非法的
They were illegal.
这些人将面临法律的全部力量
And those individuals will face the full force of the law.
我现在将回答问题
I will now take questions.
华盛顿邮报
Washington Post.
我知道这些逮捕与...
I understand these arrests are linked to...
去年在欧洲城市发生了一系列杀戮事件
a series of killings in European cities last year.
中情局参与了这些行动吗？
Was the CIA involved in those operations?
你不会指望我回答这个问题
You would not expect me to answer that.
NBC 举报人是否仍受雇于该机构？
NBC. Is the whistleblower still employed by the agency?
我可以确认警官是安全的
I can confirm that the officer is safe.
他们将继续为该机构服务
And that they will continue to serve with the agency.
现在谁是Uber司机？
Who's the Uber driver now?
你一定快没生命了
You must be running out of lives.
你总是让我吃惊，查理
And you keep on surprising me, Charlie.
你教我的一切
Everything you taught me.
不，不 你做了什么，你变成了什么...
No, no. What you've done, what you've become...
不能教这个
can't teach that.
我想我只是突然看到需要做什么
I guess I just suddenly saw what needed doing.
是啊.
Yeah.
当没有其他人做的时候
When no one else did.
谢谢
Thank you.
再见，查理
See you around, Charlie.